You mean this guy Ken
was at the bar on the 7th
waiting to make a move on a girl.
And that girl was the faceless corpse?
I remember after my hike on the 8th,
I bought something to drink at the store.
At a distance, I saw a man chasing a girl
and followed her up the hill.
(Closed for 7 days for renovation)
No...
YY!
Elsa!
Are you OK?
What are you doing here?
Since you were so keen on finding Ken, so...
I tried my way to find him.
I went back to Tender Bar...
Lee finally remember
he always paid his tab with the
university credit card.
Ken always used a credit card
from Hong Kong Island University
to pay his tab.
So I went looking for him at the university.
I saw you when I arrived
and I saw that guy.
I guess he must be Ken.
I was worried about you,
so I sent you a message.
Where are you now?
But you didn't answer.
You followed us because you were worried?
I followed you here and saw you
go up the elevator.
The other elevator was out of order
so I took the stairs.
I heard you screaming when I got up here.
I broke the fire alarm
to make him open the door.
Luckily you found me.
Lee already told me Ken was a creep.
I can't believe I was stupid enough
to follow him here.
Did you get hurt just now?
I'm fine. As long as you're not hurt.
You OK?
I'm fine.
We're stuck.
Hello? We're stuck on the 5/F.
Can you send someone?
Right away.
Don't be scared.
I'm not because you're here.
I'll watch over you.
You OK?
I'm fine.
We fixed the voltage.
The elevator should be working.
Are you OK?
We're fine. Thank you.
Here's your phone.
Thanks.
There's still no signal.
I have. I'll call the Police.
What are you doing? No Police.
I'll be in big trouble.
He kidnapped you. No Police?
I was anxious to find my sister
and let Ken conned me out here.
He didn't exactly kidnap me.
This is not kidnapping?
Did he ask you for money?
That's kidnapping.
No Police!
Why are you so scared of the Police?
Don't ask, OK?
If you called the Police,
you'll never see me again.
I'll take you home.
No need to take me home. I'll manage.
Hello? I have the money.
I'm on my way over. Don't hurt Elsa.
Daddy, it's me.
Elsa, don't worry.
I'm on my way over to save you.
Relax! I'm safe now.
I got away already.
I'm taking a taxi home right now.
Good...that's really great...
Why won't Elsa call the Police?
Because of her sister?
Not until Ken is arrested,
he may come after Elsa again.
I must find him.
Elsa!
Daddy!
Are you OK?
You scared me to death!
Your Mom went out.
I dared not tell her about your kidnapping.
I didn't want her to worry.
Before she comes home,
tell me exactly what happened.
Last time I went to Tender Bar with Emma,
I found out she had a boyfriend called Ken.
It was Ken who kidnapped me.
Emma had a boyfriend and didn't tell me?
He kidnapped you?
How did you get away?
While he wasn't looking, I snuck out.
Who is this Ken?
Daddy, he's a creep.
I think he might have kidnapped Emma.
Elsa, I need to tell you something.
I think...Emma is dead.
Dead? How come?
She just texted me she was safe.
I think that text message
was sent by someone posing as Emma.
Ken killed Emma?
No way, no way, Emma is smart.
She must have gotten away.
The Police came to see me at the hospital
and asked me about chocolate cyst.
On the faceless corpse,
they found a 4cm chocolate cyst
on the left side of the pelvic peritoneum.
It was the same location as Emma.
I'm sure that was Emma.
Emma...
Emma's death must be a major blow to Mom.
When she comes home, let me tell her.
We're heartbroken about Emma.
But we must face reality.
There's something very important...
People must not know about Emma's death
or the Police will show up at our doorstep
and find out about you.
We must keep our normal life.
If anyone should ask about Emma,
just say she's studying abroad.
I'll arrange for us to leave ASAP.
I'll talk to you when I'm safe.
Emma, please don't go.
I don't want you to go.
I'll contact you, silly.
Elsa, since you're scared,
you can sleep with me.
Great!
That's him.
He used a credit card from HKIU
to pay his bar tab.
So I used Ken and HKIU as key words
and found his account.
That's brilliant!
He's with the Band Society at HKIU
and has a studio in Wing King
Industrial Building.
Wait, Lee gave you the address?
I have my ways.
Just like you have yours, right?
You're doing my job?
What matters is you can prove
he's the killer
and get him busted.
It won't be easy to prove someone
is the killer.
But we'll bring him in for questioning.
All our leads are dead ends.
We can't even ID the body.
We only found a watch in her pocket.
What kind of watch?
C628, with the initials EH engraved
on the watchband.
It's probably the initials of her name.
Emma, you said you were tired
and didn't want to go to the spa with Mom.
So unlike you to come to
the library with me.
And you're reading that stack?
Who says you must read them?
I need them to rest my head so I can sleep.
I can't believe you're doing this...
Elsa...what's wrong?
Nothing.
You haven't been in touch.
Is Ken bothering you?
No. Something happened at home. I'm busy.
What happened?
Nothing.
Is it about your sister?
No.
I truly want to help you.
Is this your sister's watch?
That's a C628.
Me and my sister each have one.
We both had our initials EH
engraved on the watchband.
Where did you get this picture?
Kwan Sir found it in the faceless
corpse's pocket.
It had EH engraved on it, just like yours.
Is my sister really dead?
This is my feature assignment.
That's why I've been following this case.
As I dig deeper,
I'm worried you might be involved.
How did you know?
You do your reading at the library.
I suspect you don't have an ID card.
Last time you went to Tender Bar,
you left as soon as the Police showed up.
When Ken kidnapped you,
you refused to call the Police.
There must be a problem.
What happened at home?
I can't tell you.
I don't want my family in trouble.
Because I know Kwan Sir?
And because I'm a reporter?
You have qualms about me?
I won't force you,
but I want you to know,
I care about you not because
I have a story to write.
I genuinely care about you
and want to help you.
You won't write this in your story?
Everything you tell me won't go to print.
You're my friend, I won't betray you.
You saved me and have been a great help.
You guessed most of it already.
I might as well tell you.
But you must promise you won't
call the Police
or tell anyone about this.
I promise.
That's the gist of the story.
After what happened to Emma,
Daddy still won't let us call the Police.
He was afraid they'd find out about us.
But I'm not resolved.
Ken was Emma's boyfriend.
How could he kill her?
Your sister was carrying so much cash.
I'm not surprised he did it for the money.
How can we prove Ken is the killer?
You said he received your sister's messages.
If Ken has her phone, that's enough proof.
But how can we find Ken?
What a shame we can't involve the Police!
YY, why don't you tell Kwan Sir about me.
Then he'll know Ken is related to Emma.
But we can't tell him you have no ID
or the victim was your sister.
That would be tough.
I already gave Kwan Sir a hint
Ken is dangerous.
If he's keeping tabs on him,
I think you should be safe.
I don't want Emma to die
under dubious circumstances.
Help me figure something out, YY.
Don't worry!
I'll do my best to find Ken.
I'll tell Kwan Sir once I found him, OK?
Oh dear. It's Daddy. I must go.
I'll take you home.
No. I don't want Daddy to know about you.
I'll go home by myself.
We're mourning your sister.
Come and say goodbye to her.
Emma...I missed you so much.
You said you'll always be my sister.
You'll always be in my heart.
Emma died a horrible death.
I want to release her from suffering.
I already told you we must act normal.
We can't do anything out of the ordinary.
Besides, we're leaving next week.
So quick? Can you manage?
I took one week off.
When we're safe and settled down,
I'll call the hospital and quit.
The rest are pretty much taken care of.
Is there no other way?
We can't just pack up and leave!
We must leave while we can.
What are we waiting for?
We haven't caught Emma's killer.
I'm not leaving.
I want to know how she died.
If the Police caught the killer,
we'll find out wherever we are.
What's the use of waiting around?
If we want the family intact,
we must leave together.
Emma is gone.
The family is not intact.
Elsa...if we don't leave together,
this family will fall apart.
Elsa, I can't afford to lose you, too.
Please leave with us, OK?
OK?
We don't care who the killer was?
We do nothing about Emma's death?
Hello?
Elsa, I found a way
to know your sister's whereabouts.
If we know where she has been,
there's a chance we'll find Ken.
How?
(Transactions for past 30 days)
I wouldn't know if you didn't tell me,
Emma linked her Hong Kong Pass
account to her email.
I sent an email
and accessed her transaction records.
Luckily, she used the same password
for her email and Instabook,
or else you couldn't have logged in.
Check the invoices now.
It says here, the first day Emma left,
she went to restaurants,
convenience stores and bars.
Up until Day 3,
I can see all the transactions.
You're brilliant, YY!
We must check out all these places.
But Emma stopped using this card
after the third night.
Should we focus on Day 3?
I'm not busy tomorrow.
I'll go with you tomorrow.
I'm not sure if I could come out.
It's OK. Mom is not feeling well lately.
I can wait till she takes her
sleeping pills and goes to bed
before I sneak outside.
It's OK. I'll start checking.
I can't talk now. I need to work.
Bye!
I better not tell him I'm leaving.
Let's focus on finding Ken.
(The next day)
Hello, YY!
That night, your sister ate at this
pizza place.
The waitress said she was alone.
You went out so early?
I want to visit all the places your sister
went to within today.
The sooner I find Ken,
the safer you will be.
You hit every place on the list?'
You're so efficient.
I'm a special agent held up
by his reporter's duties.
CIX, MIA and MIB are trying to recruit me.
What have you found out, Agent YY?
Nothing yet.
Don't worry, just a few more on the list.
I'll find Ken for sure within the day.
Why is it shaking?
Elsa, sorry! You're in my behind.
What?
I'm helping a pretty girl with
some heavy lifting. No hands.
I have a few more boxes. Talk to you later.
Thanks, handsome. This is for you.
I should thank you.
Well?
Elsa, one good turn deserves another.
The pretty girl remembers your sister
came by on the 6th.
She mentioned she was going to
Par Par Party Room.
Hello, are you here for Zita's
birthday party?
No, we're looking for someone.
Between the 6th and the 12th,
have you seen this girl?
No.
I'm sure she was here.
Can you please look again? It's important.
The venue is booked for a birthday party.
I'm sorry I can't help you.
Hello, are you the performing guests?
Yes!
You can set up over here.
Thanks.
Sorry, can we see your CCTV?
Who are you?
The CCTV involves privacy issues.
We can't show it to you.
Thanks.
I wonder if Zita invited Ken.
He disappeared after he borrowed
a few thousand dollars from me.
He lost all the money he borrowed from
the finance company in the stock market.
Why did you lend him money?
We better start looking for
another bass guitarist.
Excuse me...the Ken you were
talking about,
is he from the HKIU Band Society?
Yes, he's in our band from school.
We're looking for Ken.
Do you know where I can find him?
I saw him with a girl last week
in Tsimshatsui.
With her?
I think so.
Do you remember where in Tsimshatsui?
Somewhere near a guesthouse.
But I forgot the name.
Anything nearby you remember?
Nearby?
Thanks.
What? I'm not finished...
Police!
Who's in charge?
Sir, what is it?
Someone called the Police
and reported a missing diamond ring.
Who made the call?
I did.
Before I went to the toilet,
I left the ring on the table.
When I came out, it was gone.
I need you all to step over here.
Get your ID cards ready.
Let us take your names and statements.
Hey, you two! Where are you going?
Stop! Come back...
You OK?
I'm fine.
Where did they go?
Let's go that way.
I think they're gone.
It's late. I should head home.
I'll try to sneak out again tomorrow
and we'll go look.
OK!
I'll check out the guest houses in the area.
Bye!
Luckily, Daddy is not home yet.
I'll go change and check on Mom.
We haven't hugged and chatted for so long.
Did you go out just now?
Since you were asleep,
I went to the library.
At this hour? What for?
Did something happen?
No, nothing happened.
You know you can always talk to me.
Let me ask you a hypothetical question.
Given my background,
if and when I meet a guy I like,
what are my chances of starting
a relationship with him?
If you knew there will be problems
and still went ahead to
start a relationship,
it's hard to say if it's a good thing.
I don't get it.
It's enough that we're in love.
I was lucky to have met Daddy.
He's a very good man
and he loves me very much.
Unfortunately, we met at the
wrong time and wrong place.
What do you mean?
You've always been happy with Daddy.
Remember you asked me before
why I didn't return to my homeland?
I wanted to, but I can't.
I was married to a drunk.
He used to beat me up when he lost
money in gambling.
You divorced him to marry Daddy?
Daddy and I were never registered
for marriage.
In order to pay for that creep's debts,
he made me a whore.
I thought I would spend the rest
of my life like that.
But Heaven opened another door for me.
A good friend found me a job here.
I secretly left that creep and came
to Hong Kong
where I met Daddy
and we decided to be together.
Can't you just go back and
divorce that creep?
Because of my homeland's religious belief,
divorce is not allowed.
Daddy didn't want me to go back.
I stayed in Hong Kong and eventually
overstayed my visa.
That's why Emma and I can't get an ID card.
I was selfish.
Without an ID card,
there's so much you can't do.
You should come to my homeland with me
so you can get an ID card.
Though I don't have an ID card,
if I met someone who loves me
as much as Daddy loves you,
it'll be OK.
It's not that simple, silly.
I don't want you to go through life
like I did.
You should come with me.
I'd like you to meet a friend
from my homeland
who will help us go home.
Mom, I'm a bit tired.
I'll wait for you at home.
OK, go on home.
See you later.
See you.
I forgot to buy cheese.
I thought she was going home.
Why is she going to Tsimshatsui?
Before I leave,
I must try to find Ken with YY.
I want to see more of him.
(Bo On Hotel)
Hello, folks.
By the hour or spend the night?
No, we're looking for someone.
Have you seen him?
And what if I did?
Can we watch your CCTV?
No problem. This guy's name is Ken.
He came with a chick.
Emma!
Here's the CCTV. Go to Room 1.
Here...
(Day 1 after Emma left)
That's Emma! She was here.
Why didn't Ken stay with her?
(Day 2 after Emma left)
Where did she go by herself?
(Second night after Emma left)
She was alone the whole time.
Why didn't Ken come back with her?
(Day 3 after Emma left)
Ken was not with her at all. That's odd.
(Day 3 after Emma left at 5:00 pm)
That's Ken!
Why did he steal the key?
He went inside Emma's room!
YY, fast forward.
(2 minutes later)
There's Emma!
Fast forward and see what happened.
That's Emma! Was she bleeding?
Yes!
What happened?
Why did she leave in a hurry?
It's Ken!
He's holding Emma's backpack.
What's going on?
Where is he going?
Why is he after her?
Thanks.
On the 8th, Ken had a fight
with the girl.
Do you know what happened?
We never butt into other people's business.
After they left, did the girl come back?
No. Neither did.
Thanks.
Excuse me, is it time's up for me?
Yes. It's time.
Here's the key.
Thanks.
From the CCTV, they didn't look like
boyfriend and girlfriend.
But Emma told me Ken was her boyfriend.
Anyhow, Emma was bleeding when
she came out.
It's definitely Ken's doing.
Maybe he wanted to take all the money.
That's why he went after your sister.
Now that we have the CCTV footage,
why don't we hand it to the Police?
I don't think we should go to the Police.
Once they start to investigate,
they may find out you don't have an ID.
The CCTV footage didn't show
Ken making any moves.
It can only prove he had a motive.
How about this?
I'm leaving Hong Kong in a few days.
By then, you can give the footage
to the Police.
You're leaving?
I'm leaving with Mom and Daddy
in a few days.
When will you be back?
Not for a while.
I didn't really want to leave,
but Daddy was afraid if we stayed,
the Police will eventually find out
we have no IDs.
That's why he decided to take Mom
back to her hometown.
We'll never see each other again?
Your name, Sir?
Big Keung sent me.
Let's go.
Wait, buddy!
How long will it take to get to
Meow Lung Kee?
What?
I heard of Meow Lung Kee.
We'll go to Meow Lung Kee in a few days
and we're all set.
Can I run to the toilet across the street?
Let me remind you,
if you miss this ride, the next one
is in two weeks.
I'll take a picture.
This may be related to Ken.
(Kwan Sir)
Kwan Sir?
You told me before there's something
fishy about this Ken.
We found out he's skipping town tonight.
Have you heard anything?
Ken is running away tonight?
Let me go find out. Call you back.
Bye!
What? Ken is skipping town?
Hurry up and tell him what we found out.
No. You're still in Hong Kong.
No, maybe nothing will happen.
Why?
When I went to HKIU to look for Ken,
I told him I was Emma's sister.
Emma's sister?
He looked quite stunned. He didn't know.
I don't understand.
When Emma left,
she promised she won't tell anyone
about our family.
I suspect she never told Ken about us.
Even if Ken was arrested,
he won't have much to tell.
I'll call Kwan Sir right now.
Kwan Sir, I got something.
Hello?
Elsa, where are you?
Me? I'm home.
Really? Stay home and keep an eye on Mom.
I'm busy at the hospital.
I'll be home later.
OK! Bye!
Meow Lung Kee.
Copy.
I'll get someone to follow up
on the license plate
and see if we can intercept it.
Keep in touch.
Bye!
OK, let's leave it to the Police.
Hopefully, they'll catch Ken.
Don't worry. Kwan Sir will call me
once he hears anything.
If he's arrested, this whole thing is over.
I'll take you home...somewhere nearby.
I'm leaving with Mom and Daddy
in a few days.
You're leaving?
When will you be back?
I really didn't want to leave.
We have a few more days.
Your supplies or any medication,
you must bring them with you.
They may be hard to find in a new place.
When you pack, don't worry about weight.
Bring everything you need.
Make sure you have a jacket,
don't catch a cold.
I'll wait for you to call.
I'll get off here.
Please stop the car.
(Your transaction record has been sent
to your email)
Someone checked Emma's Hong Kong Pass
transaction record on her email.
Was it Elsa?
Elsa, where are you?
Me? I'm home.
Really? Stay home and keep an eye on Mom.
I'm busy at the hospital.
I'll be home later.
Bye!
Let's meet again before I leave.
I'll wait for your message.
Mom?
Why did you come home late?
What is it?
Daddy? You said you'll be home later.
You also said you were home.
Where were you?
When I was on my way home,
I suddenly want to go to the library and...
Stop lying!
Who was that guy?
Nobody. We met at the library.
I met him once or twice.
He dropped me off on his way.
Don't worry, he doesn't know where I live.
I got out at the market.
So he's not just an ordinary friend.
Don't see him again.
I want you to stay home the next few days.
Why?
Felix, don't do this.
I saw him at the library.
He seems nice.
He's very nice and he's good to me.
So you're more than friends.
Did you tell him about your family?
You didn't tell him, right?
Yes or no?
I didn't mean to. But he was smart.
I mentioned a thing or two
and he figured out the rest.
Smart guy? What does he do?
He is...a reporter.
He promised he won't tell anyone about us.
You told a reporter about us?
Daddy, I'm a grown up.
I can tell a good guy from a baddie.
YY is a good guy.
He promised he won't tell anyone about us.
Besides, once he found out about Emma,
he tried very hard to find the killer.
Why bother?
I told you, leave that to the Police.
But the Police didn't know about Emma.
What can they do?
I just want the catch the killer.
So what if you did? Call the Police?
And get you and Mom arrested?
You won't rest until everyone is arrested?
I'm so disappointed in you.
I did everything for this family.
But you did not.
You told a reporter everything about us.
Give me your phone. Go to your room.
Get in...
I promised I won't stay.
Get in.
Let me out. I promised to go with you.
Let me just see him for the last time.
Mom...
Felix, calm down!
You want Elsa to be like Emma?
The key is for us to leave together.
I won't let her and the reporter
ruin things for us.
Kwan Sir, did you catch Ken?
We busted him. We're taking his statement.
Wait for me in the reception room
at the Station.
Elsa, did you get home?
Did anyone know you went out?
Kwan Sir just told me they arrested Ken.
Why didn't you text me?
I'm worried about you.
YY!
Kwan Sir?
How did you find Ken?
What and where is Meow Lung Kee?
Meow Lung Kee is a code name
for Ngan Kai Bay Pier in Sai Kung,
where people on the run get on
and off speedboats.
He's skipping town?
Because he killed someone?
We checked the CCTV at the guesthouse.
We confirmed the girl's name was Emma.
Ken only admitted he wounded her
and tried to take her money.
But he didn't kill her.
She said she wanted to leave town.
Since I have connections to
a human trafficking cartel,
I put her in that guesthouse
where people waiting to skip town
usually lie low for a while.
Did you contact her afterwards?
No. She's been looking for me
asking me when the boat is ready.
Look, I'm just the go-between,
I don't know how it works.
So I was dodging her
because she was a pain.
Lee, have you seen Ken?
He was here just now.
Don't know where he went.
Why did you go to the guesthouse alone
on the 8th?
I was in debt after I lost a lot of money
in the stock market.
I saw the money she took from her family.
I wanted to take it while she went out.
What are you doing?
Sir...she got all her money back.
I really didn't kill her. Trust me.
Ken said she was gone when
he went downstairs
and he went to a bonesetter.
My colleague checked out his story.
He was telling the truth.
So he had an alibi?
Not exactly.
Based on the CCTV and the medical
examiner's autopsy report,
the estimated time of death should be
between night time on the 8th and the 10th.
During this time frame,
Ken was hiding in a friend's village house.
But his friend was out of town.
So he didn't actually have an alibi.
Is it possible after he killed her,
he made up a story about being
somewhere else?
It's also possible he's not the killer.
The place we found the body was deserted.
There was only one store nearby.
We didn't get much from the store owner.
But there was a regular customer
who claimed he saw something
suspicious on the night of the 8th.
I didn't think much of it at first.
But after I came back from my trip
and saw the news of the faceless corpse,
I began to sense something fishy.
I remember after my hike on the 8th,
I bought something to drink at the store.
At a distance, I saw a man chasing a girl
and followed her up the hill.
Did you see his face?
I didn't.
He was quite far from me.
Can you describe him?
He's quite tall, at least 175 cm.
He was wearing a dark green windbreaker.
175 cm? How tall is Ken?
He's not 175 cm tall.
If the guy at the store was correct,
the man who chased the girl was not Ken.
Then who was it?
Ken gave us a vital piece of information.
He said he wasn't the victim's boyfriend.
Her boyfriend is British, someone called
Chan Lap-jim.
Look!
C628, with the initials EH engraved
on the watchband.
That's her watch!
He's not only tall.
He also has a dark green windbreaker.
He's the killer?